Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying robes drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
Then, thus, a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high.
Hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky.
Time to journey on.
On your mark.
Camel of other things.
We're on Earth, a legendary.
Hooray!
If you can show your breath,
Then we'll make some waves.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners!
Cause if you're wanted,
Then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise,
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day!
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece.
I'll be the first.
I heard it be so bad.
Just a good verse.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel.
I'm done playing, filled with the waiting.
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end!
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind.
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed!
I'm done playing through with the wave.
In every world I'm feeling alive.
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
And here we go!
We go!
It took a while, but we finally got
an eternal pose to Koala's hometown.
You hear that, Koala?
You can go back to your family.
Um, really?
Well, aren't you pretty?
Your parents will be proud to see
what a fine young lady you become?
I don't look silly!
We got rid of those old rags of yours.
You don't want them back, right?
You may feel awkward at first.
But I promise, your mom will be happy!
I should clean.
You, you gotta break that
weird habit of yours, okay?
You're just a normal girl.
This isn't Marie Joie.
Ah, just let her do what she wants.
You?
The girl was traumatized.
You can't expect her to stop that easily.
These things take time.
Sorry.
You should listen to Aladdin.
He would know. Yes.
Because you were a slave
once yourself, weren't you?
But those feelings might be
better served if you killed her.
Former slave or not, she's human.
Just like the ones who owned you.
I think we've heard enough far along.
Let me ask you a little question.
Tell me the truth.
Even though we spared your life, I bet your
parents don't give a damn about fishmen.
Humans think they're superior to everyone.
That's why there's no
point in saving a so-called
innocent child because
all of them are guilty.
She'll go home and
she'll learn to hate us.
It won't stop until we stop them.
Until we take them down a peg.
But you know that, right?
You've seen the way they
look at us, haven't you?
The fear, the contempt in their eyes.
If it were my decision, they would
all be five feet under right now.
Some humans but hardly all of them.
I think you need to look closer.
Is that so?
I see fear.
But that is not the same as contempt.
Is it because we're pirates?
Why are you so afraid of us?
Because I.
I don't know much about you.
I've heard that before.
It's true that our only exposure
to humans has been negative.
But that doesn't mean we can
judge all humans the same.
Fear comes from ignorance.
Koala, let's play a game.
See if you can figure
out which hand it's in.
There, okay, guess?
Um, that one?
Nope, too bad.
Oh, so close!
Thank you.
This is it, Koala.
Time to bid the ship farewell.
Where's your home village?
Come on.
I'll walk you to the entrance at least.
Okay.
Don't go, koala!
You can keep sailing with us!
You're a good girl, even if you're human!
Would you pull it together?
I'll tell the whole village
how great you guys are!
I'll let everyone know that
fishmen are nice and not scary!
I'll miss you! So long!
Thanks for helping me!
Bye!
Good luck out there!
You think she's cute now, but she'll be
a fish man hating bigots soon enough.
Orlong, you take that back. Huh?
Jinbei.
Enough. All right.
Always so noble.
Funny.
Three years ago, you weren't like this.
What's that?
Don't be a fool.
One girl telling her village that fish
men are nice isn't gonna change a thing
Just like poor Queen Otohime.
No one will listen and
no one will give a damn
It's koala.
Hurry don't tell her low.
I'm so glad you're back.
I missed you so much.
Uncle Tiger!
You can't sneak off yet.
Thanks, I'll miss you.
Take care now.
And I won't forget
Hachi or Aladdin either!
Even if we never see each other again,
and my heart will always be friends, okay?
I know these things happen slowly,
but by the time you grow up,?
I hope our people can finally get along.
Aha!
There you are, Fisher
Tiger of the Sun Pirates.
I'm Rear Admiral Strawberry.
We were informed that you might
be stopping on this island.
That girl was property
of the Celestial Dragons,
but we're going to look the
other way on that matter,
at least for the time being.
That is to say,
the village elders were more than willing
to sell you out as long as we spared her.
Do you know why I'm here?
You must, so I won't waste your time.
This is rather generous, all things
considered, but you're facing two charges.
Assault and escape.
What the what in the hell
is going on it's from
the same direction boss
was headed surely they
wouldn't attack him look
out at sea we're surrounded
what are they doing
here it was a damn trap.
The brat was nothing but
a ploy to lure us here.
They played us for fools.
We show them an ounce of
kindness and this happens. See?
Humans are monsters.
Those bastards
Wait no it must be tiger they want
Hey you guys guard the bow I'm gonna go
save the boss We finally agree when you
stop yapping and start throwing punches?
I know you won't let me down.
I'll take that as a compliment.
Let's go.
Hey, Arlhook, sir.
This is bad.
The ship is gonna sink.
Jump in the sea.
Our ship's done for.
Let's hijack one of them.
How is this monster still fighting back?
We're plugging him full of bullets
and he's just shrugging it off!
A monster?
You humans think I'm a monster?
We'll see!
Fire!
Did you hear that noise, Mom? It was loud.
What noise?
I was right.
Bosh!
We're admirals, sir.
The Sun Pirates came to save
Tiger. I see. It's him. Yes.
Team Bay.
My friends, I'm sorry.
Are you the one responsible for this
I do it all for justice and justice
demands I crush criminals like you
curse you do you want to die with your
captain you're not as strong as you
think human we were able to rescue our
boss from the marines as planned and
although our ship was sunk during battle
Arlong was able to secure
a new one from the enemy.
Then.
What?
What do you mean you
don't want a transfusion?
Are you crazy?
You don't have time.
You're gonna die.
You've lost far too much blood.
Whatever your feelings
are, you must reconsider.
The boss has a very rare blood type.
No one on the crew is
compatible, so we need another
option.
The blood.
They have stalked on the ship.
Would it be from fishmen?
It would be... human.
So what?
It should work.
Humans and fishmen share the same blood.
We found your type as well.
So it's settled, alright?
Now just relax. You're all good. Get away!
I would rather die than
live with their blood.
I won't put that filth in my body.
The blood of the bastards.
Who tried to kill me?
Dammit, no!
I won't take their mercy.
I will not owe them.
I won't give in to any human.
I won't
What happened?
Something changed for you to say this
I didn't want to tell
you guys this, but I,
on my last trip, that was quite
a lengthy voyage you took.
Yeah, an eventful one too.
Tell me, why are you
so adamant about this?
What did you see on your trip?
I saw human nature.
Soon after I started off on
my journey, they captured me.
In Mariejois, they made me...
I was...
a damn slave!
Boss, no!
Tiger!
I saw true human corruption,
true depravity, I barely escaped,
but then I kept thinking
about those other slaves,
so I went back, listen to me,
I lived how I chose to, against Oduhime's
will.
But I still believe in her.
I still believe that she's right.
Everyone wants peace.
Humans
and fishmen alike.
But our generation can't bring that peace.
We're bound to an ugly past.
Only children like Koala, free of
that history, can change the world.
Please, you can't tell them.
You have to hold it in.
Our tragedy and our hatred,
they must die with us.
No, it's all wrong.
You heard me.
Some humans are kind.
They know we're not so different.
I know it too.
And because I've met so
many compassionate humans,
I realize it's foolish to leave nothing
but hatred as legacy when I die.
But even though my mind understands that,
there is a devil in my
heart that cannot forgive,
that fills me with rage.
My very flesh rejects them.
It rejects their blood.
Despite all that I fought for
I cannot love them I'm sorry.
However you feel you can
work it out when this
is all done for now I'm
begging you just live.
Listen boss you're a
hero those slaves that
you set free they owe
you their very lives.
Please, boss, you can't
die. Not like this.
To every slave and every
fishman, you're a symbol of hope.
Then I'm happy.
You're still not strong enough. Damn it!
You have to step in front of your
men with your whole body. Do that.
You protect them. Huh?
Why would I...
Jinbei!
If there's no one else
who can challenge me,
I'm the new leader of
the fishman district.
Call me Tiger!
We're all brothers now.
Your blood is my blood.
So I swear that I'll protect it.
I'll fight for the
lives of every fish man.
Nooooooo!
Nooooooooooo!
Sorry, Tiger, but you're wrong!
I'll never forgive them!
All right, you punks!
Get ready to die! A fish man?
He must be from...
He's awful noisy, isn't he?
Far along, was it?
So what brings you here?
You want to start trouble that bad?
Not too smart, if you ask me.
Out of my way!
I'm going after all the lousy
humans who betrayed my captain!
And you, Navy scum, can't stop me!
Oh, so this is about revenge.
Damn straight!
You killed Fisher Tiger!
I don't care what happens to
me, but you deserve to die!
Oh, so your friend is dead, I see.
Well, you can cry if you like, but
either way, you're coming with me now.
Arlong was enraged by
Brother Tiger's death.
He took his anger out on humans
and was imprisoned as a result.
There his hatred grew.
If he had a transfusion, he'd be fine.
Instead, he had to die, because
they refused to treat fishmen.
He brought that little girl back to her
family, and you repaid that by killing him!
Fisher Tiger, captain of the Sun Pirates,
dies after being denied a
transfusion of human blood.
Not quite, though it is close.
Regardless, the captain's dead,
and humans played a big role.
Arlong lied to them.
Why would he do such a thing?
Good for him.
The truth is a lot worse.
Tiger chose to save that girl
despite his own prejudice.
Yet humans still betrayed him, so he
coldly refused to accept their blood.
On top of that, he was a slave.
If any of this became public, they
would have attacked Tiger's character.
So let Arlong tell his little white lies.
You!
Hey, Captain Jinbei!
Enemy ship ahead!
The boss may not be with us, but we
still have to keep moving forward.
Prepare yourselves!
Follow Tiger's wishes and
do not kill anyone! Yeah!
From that day forward,
I bore the title First
Son of the Sea and fought
to do my best as Captain
of the Sun Pirates.
Though in truth, fighting seemed to
be the only thing our crew was doing.
I am writing this because
I thought the two of you
deserved to know the whole
truth about what happened.
Signed, Jinbei, Captain
of the Sun Pirates.
My mind's made up.
In the end, Fisher Tiger lived
the only way that he knew how.
Poor Saul, I finally understand
the pain that he felt that day.
As their leader, I must remain strong.
I won't give in!
We too shall live under the Sun
and try to understand one another!
If I may, signing here is the first
step to harmony with all due respect.
We know, to he may, you
must be out of your mind!
Fisher Tiger freed countless
slaves, both fishmen and human.
He didn't care about what race they were.
Yet humans still refused to help him.
Who cares about understanding another?
Fruitless day without any signatures.
Mother,
you
really
need some rest.
You children brighten my day.
I'm fine!
Don't worry.
Okay, I won't.
If you say so, mother,
I'll keep doing my best
to make this world a
better place for everyone.
Queen Otohime was working
so hard, day after day.
She rescued humans from shipwrecks.
Are you all right?
Pirates must have hit them.
Please help me.
Don't worry, we're here.
Bring the wounded to the island.
She taught the island children
about the world above.
Does anybody remember what this
area with many trees is called?
You there, forest.
Like the sea forest.
And collected signatures.
Please, wait!
I just need a moment of your time!
However...
Queen Otohime!
Oh!
Hello again!
Thank you for showing your
support the other day.
Actually, about that, we're curious.
How many signatures do you have?
Well, I've been collecting
them for five years now.
One hundred sheets have been signed,
with each containing ten signatures.
So that adds up to one
thousand supporters.
Still, the population of the island is
five million, so we're not done yet.
Step by step, right?
Um, we have kind of a big favor to ask.
We'd like to withdraw our signatures.
They total about half of what you have.
Does that sound okay? Huh?
You must not have heard about it,
but those human pirates that
you rescued the other day?
They committed a robbery in town
before escaping from the island.
Your Majesty.
Queen Otohime!
Oh, hello, children.
Are you ready for another lesson yet?
Excuse me!
My mom wants that paper I
signed the other day back.
I found it! Yeah!
Go, mommy!
May I help you?
I do hope there's no hard feelings.
What with you being the queen and all.
We just can't do it.
Humans are too evil.
We'll pass on the speeches, too.
Yeah, sorry about all this.
We've just had enough.
Surprise, Mommy!
Did we scare you?
What an exhausting day.
I think I might have
overdone it a bit out there.
I'm sorry, sweeties, but could you
give your mother some alone time today?
You...
You're all...
Liars!
Your Majesty, this is on the air.
Everyone can hear you.
Why don't you shut up?
Mr.
At the Left!
Majesty, have you been drinking?
Leave me alone.
I'm not drunk at all.
Yes, you are. Goodness. What's happening?
Is that really Queen Otohime?
Everybody better listen to me!
You can live however you want.
If that means staying in this island,
then I can't stop you,
neither can anyone else.
But in the vastness of
the ocean, so broad.
And on the sea floor, foreboding and dark.
We chose this tiny place
and this place alone.
Do you have any idea why?
Queen Otohime, isn't it because this
is where we can get a bit of sunlight?
Where we can get a bit of air?
Luxuries down here are
plentiful above ground.
Light illuminates the entire surface,
and the sky stretches out
as far as you can see.
Our children why do they always sneak
out to catch a glimpse of Sabo Ori Park?
Can't you see the world is filled with
more beauty than any
of us can even imagine?
There's no place that we shouldn't be able
to go why restrict
ourselves to this bubble?
I know you tell yourselves life down
here is comfortable but you're safe.
Do you want to spend the
rest of your lives trapped?
dig deep summon your courage.
Once you have it pursue
your dreams no matter
the cost your majesty if
humans stand in your way?
We'll face them together you don't have to
confront your fears alone and maybe then?
We can finally make a difference for the
future, for our children, for the island.
Even if it's just a small one.
My goodness, you've seen better days.
He was formidable.
I see.
He certainly did a
number on you, didn't he?
Arlong, the fishman that we just locked
up and impelled down, he was nothing.
But you have to watch out for this one.
Jinbei!
He's quite strong, even
by fishman standards.
He's far too dangerous at large.
We should bring him in.
Unbelievable.
Me and the seven warlords?
Oh, it's not that surprising.
You're worth $250 million.
With a bounty that big, they definitely see
you as a threat to the world government.
That's the highest praise a
pirate can get from those chumps.
Mackerel's right.
They're finally taking us seriously.
All you need to do is reject them.
That'll really help us
pile on the notoriety.
No one will ever mess with us.
My mind is made up.
I'm going to take the navy's offer! What?
Welcome home, Jinbei.
I heard about the seven
warlords' proposal.
If I join,
Aladdin and the other crew members Who do
not wish to be pirates
No longer have to be.
They can live in this country
without fear of retribution.
It's a way for me to take care of my men.
But more importantly If
I do become a warlord?
It will help the fishermen become
closer to the world government.
We need that relationship.
I can atone for all the trouble
that we've caused the Queen.
Thank you.
At the moment, she's
not feeling very well.
In the end, we might see Tiger's dream.
Liberation and freedom for
all fishermen, everywhere.
Though, then again, we
have to watch our own.
There are some less deserving of amnesty.
Arlong!
It's really new!
So good to have your back, bro!
If you have something to say to
me, then you'd better speak up now.
Now, you expect to thank
you for becoming a sellout.
You may have set me free,
but the Navy owns you.
Have you forgotten what
Brother Ty said before he died?
You mustn't let anger and
bitterness overwhelm you.
Sounds to me like you've gotten soft.
Sure, I'd probably be safer
if I followed your lead,
but there's no way in hell I'm doing that.
You can't make me sick.
In case you forgot, Tiger is dead.
Which means I'm free.
Free to lead my own crew.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'll be taking back my men.
Got a problem with that?
You fool.
You damn ignorant fool.
Hey now, enough with the name code.
Let's end this.
Right now, just you and me.
What?
Arlong, no!
If you don't do it, I'm free to go.
Fair warning.
I won't go down easily.
You'll have to kill me!
Arrogant Paul!
Don't do this!
That's more like it.
Please, stop it!
Jimmy, no!
I wouldn't dwell on it.
There's nothing you could have done.
You've known each other
since childhood, after all.
Like him or not, he's still
like a brother to you.
And you're no killer.
He's blinded by hate.
He'll never understand.
What tiger meant by his dying
words it doesn't matter how
far he goes as long as arlong
engages in violence the navy
will be after him worst comes
to worst we may have to stop
arlong ourselves one day at
any cost only time will tell
look i'd love to stay and chat
captain jean bay but we're
headed out to good luck you're
gonna need it macro come
back here i want to leave
little so long
suckers damn it
he's stronger than i realized
you archie you can't look back
the sun pirates split into three
groups with our long macro and myself
as captains and ever since then we
have continued going our separate ways
Thank you.